Enter Dorami-chan!
Nobita's Undersea Hiking
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
What? Doraemon is going back?
Nobita, didn't you know already?
No kidding!
Doraemon, will you really go back to the 22nd century?
Yes, for a periodical maintenance.
And I've to...
No, you can't go back.
You could have maintenance anytime, can't you?
Not really.
No, you can't!
No...
You can't just go back.
Please don't, otherwise I'd have to eat ramen using my belly button!
Care to explain?
I have promised my friends that I'll take them to the Pacific Ocean.
What are you guys talking about?
We are discussing about how to spend our holiday during the Golden Week.
Note: Golden Week is a major Japanese one week-long holiday, it's time when films of popular franchises get released in film theaters.
I will practise Horizontal Bar Wheel.
I will make a stuffed Panda doll.
I will ride barge to traverse round the world in a circle.
Barge, how cool.
I envy you.
Not really.
My uncle has told me that he'll take me to the South Pole next year.
The South Pole!
I envy you more and more.
Don't you envy him as well, Nobita-kun?
Not at all...
So, what's your plans for the holidays, Nobita?
I...?
I bet that he doesn't have any plans.
Nobita loves to takes daytime naps, after all.
Alright! Don't you get surprised after you hear my plan!!!
I don't use barge,
I will walk through the middle of Pacific Ocean by foot.
By foot?
You sure you're not insane?
But of course.
But what will you do if it is a lie?
I will eat Ramen with my bellybutton.
Bellybutton?
So you sprouted nonsense again.
Please.
Please help me and don't go back! You're the only person I can rely on!
No.
I already have an appointment for the maintenance...
if I don't go now, I'll never be able to get examined.
You should at-least be able to understand that...
So, I must go back, at all costs.
Well then, I'll get going.
Sorry for being unable to help you.
I will bring you a gadget which can help you...
eat ramen with bellybutton as a souvenir.
Bye!
Cheer up, Nobita-kun.
He didn't had an option.
If Doraemon breaks one day, how terrible my life will be.
But what should I do now, Doraemon?
Sorry. Actually, I have another reason.
The day Doraemon comes back is... the last day of the Golden Week.
What a bother!
You must be exaggerating!
Who is it?
Hi!
So you must be Nobita-kun!
Why do you know me?
I told her.
Why! It's you, Doraemon! you came back for me? Thank you so much!
I was worried about you, so I'll leave you in my younger sister's care.
Sister?
I am his sister, Dorami.
Nice to meet you.
Dorami is more excellent robot than me.
So she'll help you.
Really? I'm so happy!
that a cute girl robot will take care of me.
Nobita-kun, you are riding on a wave.
|'ll go back.
OK! It is fine if you don't come back.
Dorami-chan...
Bye, bye!
Bye, bye.
Bon voyage!
How dare he say goodbye to me!?
I heard about it from my big bro.
Are you serious? About walking on the seabed?
Of course, I am.
I wanna do it for real.
Alright, I'll help you.
Stand up for a moment.
What is that?
I'll use it on you.
It is a House-Keeper Robot.
It scared the hell out of me!
|I don't know how long will you be in the pacific, Nobita-san...
It's totally unlike me!
I am more handsome.
Also... one more thing!
What's that bag?
So cool!
Seabed Travel Set!
Let me explain, listen carefully.
Air Nose Tube!
To breathe in seabed.
So you should put it on your nostrils.
You could now breathe in water.
Canned food!
Put foods in it.
One can store about 30 pieces of food.
But you shouldn't become a glutton.
Deep-Sea Latex Cream!
After you apply it on your body.. you will be able to walk even at 10,000 feet below the ocean.
And it can keep your body warm.
Transceiver and Receiver.
Compass.
Sleeping bag.
And underwater shoes...
When you wear it,
its bounce and speed in the sea is higher ten times than on the ground.
And it can keep your body in balance.
The last is the Hydraulic Pressure Gun.
We can shoot each other using bullets of water .
How cool!
We have just about anything.
With all these gadgets even oyu'll be fine, Nobita-kun.
From Japan to San Francisco, USA...
Walk in seabed and go through the Pacific Ocean.
I'm so excited!
So we head-out tomorrow at sunrise.
During my stay in the sea, please take a good care of our house.
Sure!
But you're the one who's very clumsy, so take care.
What did you say?
Bon voyage!
I wonder if that Robot can really take care of the house?
I hope so.
So you're not coming with me?
I want to come with you, but unlike my big bro...
I will rust if I am under the sea for a long time.
Dorami-chan, you're so delicate, huh?
Thanks for the compliment, Nobita-san!
Compared to you, Doraemon...
I sure wonder what Doraemon is doing now?
No, please stay still.
You worked very hard in that world.
No, I enjoyed my life.
Really?
So after you have been examined tomorrow,
I will replace some of your body parts.
Sir! I have a request.
What would that be?
I want artificial ears.
I am a Cat-Model Robot, but I'm very afraid of rats.
My ears were broken by a rat.
I see, I see.
OK.
So I will give you the best latest model ears.
Sure? Kiss!
I am ready.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am!
What souvenir do you want, Dorami-chan?
How about a conch?
Never mind that, be careful.
Dorami-chan, you're such a worry girl.
I will take the first step at last.
Here goes I!
Ouch...
I had warned you...
There's no demon in the seabed!
I lied to him that I would rust in the sea...
But to make Nobita, a independent boy, I had no other choice!
But I'm still worried about him.
How beautiful.
So here's the continent border.
At this rate, I can walk even miles..
Ah, sorry.
Oh, it's just an eel.
What?
I see.
Let's go!
What a cute fishes!
I am Nobita.
Dorami,-chan can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
I am at the continent border now.
I walked 20 km now.
Now I am having lunch.
I am fine, I walked carefully.
You don't have to worry about me.
I will call you later.
Oh, no!
Help me... Doraemon...
Doraemon...
The shark will eat me, please help!
Done.
Dorami-chan!
Dorami, do you copy?
A great accident happened just now.
There were a big shark.
And well...
Take that...!
Nobita, go and water the plants.
OK.
Nobita, this is not a yard.
is that so?
OK.
Seriously?!
Sorry, auntie.
Nobita, I'll punish you!
Ouch.
Why did you do that?
Please be quiet and have a nap.
Don't wanna take a nap!
Enough, take a nap!
It became dark.
Here is blue water.
Another big fish.
It is angel fish.
Dorami-chan, I am feeling so lonely, please sing me a song.
But I...
Any one will do.
Really!
Nobita-san sure knows how to keep me busy.
I don't want music, please save me!
I'm so scared for life...!
I got tired of you, Nobita-san!
I heard that he was a wimp.
I can now relate to big bro...
Doctor said that I could choose any ear I like.
But I'm so unsure which one to pick from...!
That one looks cool!
No, this one!
I want this one!
Nobita.
Nobita speaking..
I'm now in Japan sea.
I see no end in sight either way.
I feel as if I'm at the entrance of hell.
What's the matter, Nobita-san?
Nobita-san, do you copy?
It is snowing.
It is snowing in blue water.
Snow?
Oh, it's the marine snow!
It sticks to shrimp and gravitates in seabed.
It will shine later.
it's been a week since Nobita went to the sea...
I wonder where is he now?
Nobita and Dorami-chan, it's snack-time!
OK.
No matter how deep I go, there's no end...
When I can reach another side of the sea, I wonder?
What is it?
It is a Dorayaki.
It's Dora-chan's favorite snack!
Dorami-chan!
Nobita, you are so bad-mannered.
News
Well then, for today's news...
A volcano erupted in the seabed of Torishima Island
oh, no, Nobita-san!
Nobita-san!
Nobita-san, do you copy me?
I have replaced all the malfunctioning parts.
Right! Now all I need are the ears...
Let's begin.
Brother, Nobita-san is in danger!
Not again?
You're such a bad girl!
What the hell did you do?
Sorry.
I was eating Dorayaki with the family...
Dorayaki Where? Gimme!
I wanna eat!
Brother, it's not time to be eating.
Right, we must...
Appropriative Secondary Rocket!
Catch Nobita using this!
Right!
I was knocked out...
How many hours has it been?
I'm not hurt!
That's it, I'll call Dorami-chan!
Ah, my backpack is gone!
Transceiver-Receiver, food, electric light... all are gone!
Oh, no!
I'm stuck here in seabed!
what shall I do now?
I can't find him!
As long as we know where Nobita-kun is, we can go rescue him.
Now...
I've got to walk...
Walk...
I'm so lost!
It's a submarine!
Hey! Help... Help...
What...?
Come save me quickly...
I won't let you go without me!
Found him.
Oh, no!
My hands are slippery!
Who will save me?
Doraemon! Dorami-chan!
Nobita-kun!
Doraemon!
Where are we?
How strange! We'd be home I suppose.
The submarine researched volcano under the seabed and saw a person there...
Really, I wonder?
That's me!
There was a person there, it says!
Yup!
If you want to tell a lie, come up with a better one.
i hope that you will eat ramen with your bellybutton...
I didn't lie! I went there...
Then show us any evidence?
Evidence...?
Right, where is the evidence?
Brother, you were unable to get ears...
Yes, I didn't, but...
I don't mind that as long as Nobita-kun is safe.
Big Bro!
Doraemon!
Please take out a gadget to eat noodles with my bellybutton!
Giant and Suneo are merciless...
Please help me, Doraemon!
Oh, brother...
It looks like Bro will remain with Nobita-san for a long while now!